A Finding Aid to the Rose Fried Gallery Records, 1936-1972, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artists and Clients Files, 1936-1972; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 7.9 Linear feet Boxes 1-8, OV 9
  - V Miscellaneous, 1960-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Walker Art Center, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Weidemann, Guillerme, 1965-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, York, General, 1965-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, York, Photographs, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Winston, Harry and Lydia, 1953-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Winter, Ella, 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Woodman, George Edgar, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1961-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Xceron, Jean, 1946-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16-23)
  - XXe Siecle, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1961-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Yates, Sidney R., 1961-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Yepes, E., 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Yunkers, Adja, 1957-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28-32)
  - Y Miscellaneous, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Zachs, Sam and Hyala, 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Zetlin, Florence, 1960-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Zeisler, Richard, 1959-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Unlabeled, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Oversized Leo Manso from Box 5, Folder 13, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 9)